Foolish.
You should have just abandoned that useless human.
Yuliy...
Get out of here...
I will.
With you by my side!
Well then...
It's about time to put an end to this!
Ready!
Fire.
Fire! Keep it up!
Don't give the monsters a chance to counterattack!
As I thought, the rounds from V Shipping are quite effective.
What happened?
I'd say our luck's turned around!
It would seem that the army's here.
Even our marvelous brethren might not hold for long.
They'll be no real threat.
I'll leave him to you.
Though I do regret that I won't be able to watch the last two Sirius fight to the death.
You heard the man.
What is this?
Why has the army started a firefight in my mansion?
Father, it's too dangerous to leave right now!
I'm going to talk to their commander! They seem to think that they're stationed in Ryojun!
Well now, Mister Willard.
We mobilized all of these troops in order to get revenge for the incident during the exercises in Fuji.
We will find the Alma Company manager who tried to sell
us a monster by calling it a "new type of weapon," right?
Yes.
With certainty.
What's wrong?
If you don't come at me with a mind to kill, you're finished.
I'm not going to kill you.
Even if you're a vampire,
you're still my brother!
Soft.
You really aren't cut out for taking revenge.
Who can take my place, then?
Who else can put the souls of Mom and the other villagers to rest?
You think you'll be able to take your revenge by killing every vampire?
Do you honestly believe that?
Long before you'll be able to kill all of them,
they will surely reach what they seek.
You mean...
The Ark of Sirius.
But the Ark is long—
Exactly. When they came to Dogville ten years ago it was already gone.
Do you know why?
I...
Because Dad left with it.
Dad?
Why—
Yuliy.
You're the last of the Sirius.
Make use of what my vampire blood has taken from me, and do the thing that only you can do.
What are you—
Yuliy.
Live.
Brother?
Brother!
Yuliy!
Philip!
We're here!
Take care of Philip!
Yuliy!
Damned impudent humans.
Willard?
Professor Willard?
Now this is quite the surprise.
I'd doubted my ears when I was told that there was a remnant of the Sirius among the Jaegers,
but if you're his owner then everything makes sense.
You look older, Professor.
But of course you would.
Ten years is a terribly long time for a human, after all.
Yes, it's been a long time indeed,
Kershner!
Perhaps you would have been better suited for the lectern.
Professor?
Well, this is unexpected.
Is Mikhail dead?
My brother disappeared.
So he chose the life of his brother over his loyalty to us.
What a useless mongrel.
Shut up!
Get away from the Professor!
He seems awfully fond of you.
How on earth did you tame him so well after what you did to him?
What are you talking about?
Now this is rich!
You're quite the fiend yourself, Professor!
Very well!
In place of your taciturn master, I'll tell you a story!
Make sure to thank me at the end.
Once upon a time, we obtained a certain ancient text.
In it was a story about the Ark of Sirius.
In it was also written its location.
The location of Dogville.
Can't you remember?
Don't these flames remind you of the ones you saw that day?
You...
It was you!
Let's not get ahead of ourselves.
My story is not yet over, little Sirius.
We were having trouble deciphering the contents of that text, you see.
So we decided to have a certain human archaeologist do it for us.
An impoverished scholar who was passionately investigating the location of the Ark of Sirius.
When we presented him with an offer of patronage, he jumped at the chance.
He was ever so thankful, wasn't he?
He did excellent work.
Thanks to that scholar making sense of the text for us,
we were able to lift the veil on Dogville.
You see what I'm trying to say, right?
No, that's impossible!
You're quite the foolish pup.
You're lying.
The Professor?
It is as he says.
Great fortune is upon you, remnant of the Sirius!
Two of the men you must kill are gathered before you tonight!
So you've finally shown your true nature!
Do you hate me?
Do you want to kill me?
How pathetic!
To think that we would one day have to depend on the treasure of a people so pathetic!
Stop—
Impossible!
You inelegant...
animal...
Come.
Why?
Why did you never tell me?
It was all because of my ego.
I thought that saving a young wolf who'd lost his family and kin would serve as my atonement.
But then I led you to choose revenge as a reason to live.
I ended up using you as a tool for my revenge.
Even though I was really one of the targets of yours.
But I thought I could live with that,
so long as the moment you learned the truth was the moment I died.
That time has come.
Shut the hell up.
Do you think that's all these ten years were?
Even with the blood of a beast—
With my Sirius blood washing my vision red,
my hand stopped.
Do you understand why?
You've been my rock for all these years!
It was because you were like a father to me that...
Yuliy...
If it wasn't for you, my story would have ended then.
It was because you were there for me that I've lived this long.
Why...
Why did my mother and the other villagers have to die?
Why did my brother have to become a vampire?
Is it all because of the Ark?
Please tell me, Professor!
Professor Willard!
As the remnant of the Sirius,
I must know everything.
Bureau of Military Affairs
Head Office
Major!
That was quite a chewing-out.
Do you have a report?
Yes, sir.
There were no corpses to be found at the scene of last night's battle.
The police are losing their minds.
It seems that there's some advantage to turning to ash when you die.
"Vampires," was it?
I'm still having trouble believing it.
But do you think that General Kakizaki and the soldiers who died at Fuji can rest in peace now?
So I hope.
What are they doing with the Ninth Floor Annex?
A good old fashioned order to disband due to abuse of authority.
I see.
That's unfortunate.
I'm sorry about this.
I'll be heading back to Harbin.
They told me to be glad I'm not being court-martialed.
Have you not been told?
There was someone else who's issued a summons for you.
Wha... wha...
What is this!
Hello, Sensei!
M-Miss Ryouko!
What... The mansion! The dojo!
Where's the Baron?
He wasn't hurt, but the shock of it all has left him unable to get out of bed.
I can't blame him.
Don't worry about it, Miss Ryouko.
V Shipping will pay reparations for the house and everything else lost in the fire.
T-They will?
You're so lucky.
I wish vampires would rip down my wreck of a house back home.
What?! What are you people say—
Um!
Where are Yuliy and Professor Willard?
They're a little bit busy right now.
I learned of the existence of the Ark while searching for Dogville.
An "ark of miracles," protected by the Sirius for generations.
Within it lie all kinds of knowledge and technologies.
To humanity, it's like wisdom itself in physical form.
So said the legends, anyway.
Back then, I simply wanted to discover whether it really existed or was just a fairy tale.
I guess your patrons wanted a bit more than that.
Indeed.
There must be something the vampires need among the knowledge and technologies the Ark holds.
So my father knew what the Ark was, then.
That's why he took it away from the village.
From my research, I gathered that the Ark was to be
protected by one with the blood of the Sirius in their veins.
If he's alive, then he's most likely protecting the Ark somewhere, but if he isn't...
"You need to do the thing that only you can do."
My brother said that.
What only I can do,
what only a remnant of the Sirius can do.
If that thing is protecting the Ark of Sirius...
If there's something I can do for my slain mother and kin other than hunting vampires...
Then I want to look for the Ark.
I see.
We probably don't have much time left.
Kershner was merely a pawn.
The name of the vampire who truly desires the Ark is Yevgraf.
He's most likely closer than anyone else to finding the Ark.
From the east to the west coast...
So it's spread over almost the entire continent.
Yes, lord.
The sickness is spreading to the whole world.
A veil of death, descending upon our entire race...
Lord Yev, Lord Yev!
News from Tokyo!
They said Kershner's dead!
He's dead!
What about Mikhail?
They said that Misha and
Grampa Klarw are coming to meet us!
To meet us!
Is that so.
Then there's no problem.
Yuliy, I fixed your coat—
What, you all helped clean up for like five minutes and already need a break?
Come on, we're all tired from yesterday!
On top of that, I'll have you know that I'm injured.
Oh yeah, so's Yuliy.
Yeah.
This is nothing, though.
True.
Your body is pretty crazy, after all.
Yeah.
Man, I'm hungry.
Where's the Professor?
He said he had to go contact headquarters.
Hey.
The owner of this place helped me out a bit.
I came to drink one in his name.
I didn't take you for the dutiful type.
What are you planning to do now?
Are you going after more vampires?
Or perhaps the Ark of Sirius?
That could affect the very existence of the Empire.
You would have me believe such a thing really exists?
An understandable reaction.
However, if I, for instance, said to your face that there's no such thing as vampires,
could you present any proof that there are?
Captain Akasaka Mamoru.
This man received top-secret orders to find and acquire the Ark of Sirius.
However, fifteen years ago we lost contact with him while he was in central Asia.
Thanks to the Great War, searching for the captain was low on our list of priorities.
Due to the recent global depression and the situation with the mainland,
we decided to give the Ark our attention again.
Major Iba.
We'd like you to covertly search for the Ark of Sirius in Captain Akasaka's place,
and find and acquire it before any other country has the chance to.
The fate of the Empire will depend on whether we have possession of the Ark or not.
As unbelievable as that may sound.
Why am I being entrusted with such a vital mission?
Moreover, I still don't have enough information to complete it.
V Shipping...
Or rather, the Jaegers, right?
Anyway, you're in contact with a man who works for them named "Willard."
He was once considered the greatest living expert on legends about the Sirius in academic circles.
We've learned of the events that prompted you to bring troops to the Naoe residence.
As expected of Intelligence's rising star.
You're the man's friend now, aren't you?
So just because I helped you,
I got stuck doing this crap.
An unfortunate turn of events.
If you're not just saying that, then help me out here.
Have you ever seen the man in this picture?
No.
But there is something else I could tell you.
The vampires are also after the Ark of Sirius.
What?
After I informed headquarters that we've completed our mission here in Japan,
they replied that the vampire that's searching for the Ark, Yevgraf, was seen at Karafuto.
Karafuto?
Are we even now, Major Iba?
More than even.
By the way, Mister Willard,
are you not after the Ark anymore?
I'm not.
Searching for the Ark isn't my specialty anymore.
That's disappointing.
Yevgraf?
I've never heard that name before.
So are we going to that "Karafuto" place now?
No.
Another team's headed there.
We've been ordered to go to London and report in at headquarters.
London?
We're finally going back to Europe!
I feel like we're probably the closest team to Karafuto right now, though.
Orders from Headquarters are absolute.
What's wrong, Yuliy?
It's nothing.
What, do you not like my hometown?
I'd be happier if it at least had some decent grub.
What? Your country's no different!
It most certainly is!
What an unbearable end
I breath out, breath out, breath out, and stop
As I'm fleeing from this cruel world, I fall into a deep sleep
I hide behind the words "I'm doing my best"
But in the end I do nothing but look back
Even when I feel like I've been able to change,
Eventually I realize that the only thing that's changed is the position of the stars
I find myself wondering if everything would feel better if I just broke
Before I fade away while thinking of you,
If I dig out all of my pain then I'll be able to shine like a real star
Will I find a beautiful dream?
This is how we embrace hope
Yokohama
Karafuto
It's not like I don't like being with everyone or being a Jaeger anymore.
It's just...
I've found it.
I've found what I should really do.
Yuliy, we are a cooperative pack.
We chase our prey wherever
they flee, corner them, and eliminate them.
That's our job.
I liked the idea of being part of a pack like that.
But this is something I have to do by myself.
And so, I'm saying goodbye.
An eternal seal, unbreakable to all the world.
Are you really a Jaeger?
Why don't you become a vampire, too?
Don't interfere!